A Guide to the Commonwealth Fund records, Task Force on Health Insurance, SG 3, Series 10 FA1470
Rockefeller Archive Center
Commonwealth Fund records, Task Force on Health Insurance, SG 3, Series 10
1994-2000
Rockefeller Archive Center
Commonwealth Fund
FA1470
1.14 Cubic Feet Three letter-size document boxes.
Arrangement
Original order, as received.
Conditions Governing Access
Open for research. Brittle or damaged items are available at the discretion of RAC.
Immediate Source of Acquisition
The Commonwealth Fund records were donated to RAC in 1985. The initial transfer of archival records to RAC began in 1986, and transfers continue on a regular basis. This series was transferred to RAC as accession 2007:055.
Scope and Contents
The Task Force on Health Insurance series contains grant administration files from The Henry J. Kaiser Family Foundation/Commonwealth Fund Low Income Coverage and Access Project: State Case Studies, Phase Two (Grant Number: 980198). The material documents the plannng and implementation of the study including: proposals, administration and budget files, grant products, reports and papers, related correspondence and background material.
- Mathematica Policy Research, Inc. - Gold (980198) - Administration and Budget, 1998-1999 (Box 1, Folder 1)
- Mathematica Policy Research, Inc. - Gold (980198) - Articles and Background (Box 1, Folder 2)
- Mathematica Policy Research, Inc. - Gold (980198) - Correspondence, 1997-1999 (Box 1, Folder 3)
- Mathematica Policy Research, Inc. - Gold (980198) - Proposal Development, 1997 (Box 1, Folder 4)
- Mathematica Policy Research, Inc. - Gold (980198) - Grant Products, 1998-1999 (Box 1, Folder 5-6)
- Mathematica Policy Research, Inc. - Gold (980198) - Board Book Write Up, 1994-1997 (Box 1, Folder 7)
- Mathematica Policy Research, Inc. - Gold (980198) - California, 1999 (Box 1, Folder 8)
- Mathematica Policy Research, Inc. - Gold (980198) - Florida, 1998 (Box 2, Folder 9)
- Mathematica Policy Research, Inc. - Gold (980198) - Maryland, 1998 (Box 2, Folder 10)
- Mathematica Policy Research, Inc. - Gold (980198) - Minnesota, 1998-1999 (Box 2, Folder 11)
- Mathematica Policy Research, Inc. - Gold (980198) - Oregon, 1998 (Box 2, Folder 12)
- Mathematica Policy Research, Inc. - Gold (980198) - Tennessee, 1998 (Box 2, Folder 13)
- Mathematica Policy Research, Inc. - Gold (980198) - Texas, 1999 (Box 3, Folder 14)
- Mathematica Policy Research, Inc. - Gold (980198) - Cross-cutting, 1998 (Box 3, Folder 15)
- Mathematica Policy Research, Inc. - Gold (980198) - Cross-cutting Tables, 1999 (Box 3, Folder 16)
- Mathematica Policy Research, Inc. - Gold (980198) - Medicaid Managed Care-SSI Behavioral Health, 1999-2000 (Box 3, Folder 17)
- Mathematica Policy Research, Inc. - Gold (980198) - Florida Notes and Paper, 1998-1999 (Box 3, Folder 18)
- Mathematica Policy Research, Inc. - Gold (980198) - Tennessee Notes, 1997 (Box 3, Folder 19)